#The dictionary for they questions & answers (need to insert them in the mongodb shell)

db.questions.insert({'question':'Where was Techno developed?','answer':'a','options':['a.Detroit, Michigan','b.Kalamazoo, Michigan','c.Auburn, Michigan','d.Memphis, Michigan']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'Which novel was an inspiration to develop Techno genre of music?','answer':'b','options':['a.Futurewise','b.Future Shock','c.The Improving State of the World','d.Brave New World']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'When was Techno developed?','answer':'c','options':['a.during the mid to late 1960s','b.during the mid to late 1970s','c.during the mid to late 1980s','d.during the mid 1960s']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'Who had developed the phrase "techno rebels"?','answer':'a','options':['a.Alvin Toffler','b.James Maury','c.Marshall Brain','d.Benjamin M. Friedman']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'Which of the following were known as "Belleville Three" in the parlance of Techno music?','answer':'d','options':['a.Eddie Fowlkes,Derrick May,Juan Atkins','b.Eddie Fowlkes,Juan Atkins,Kevin Saunderson','c.Derrick May,Juan Atkins,Kevin Saunderson','d.Juan Atkins,Kevin Saunderson,Derrick May']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'Which of the following is the sub-genres of Techno music?','answer':'a','options':['a.All of them','b.Ambient','c.Minimal','d.Acid']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'What are the instruments utilized by the original techno producers based in Detroit?','answer':'d','options':['a.Roland TB-303 bass line generator','b.Roland TR-808 drum machine','c.Roland SH-101 synthesizers','d.All of them']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'Which of the following artists are heavily influenced by Techno?','answer':'c','options':['a.Madonna','b.U2','c.Both of them','d.Britney Spears']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'Which of the following are are considered early examples of techno music?','answer':'d','options':['a."IBM Probe"','b."The Bass-Line Generator"','c."The Rhythm Modulator"','d.All of them ']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'Techno music has been used in the following film:','answer':'c','options':['a.Blade','b.Matrix','c.Both of them','d.Speed 2']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'In which countries was Techno virtually ignored during the late 1980s and early 90s?','answer':'d','options':['a.UK','b.Belgium','c.Germany','d.U.S.A.']})
db.questions.insert({'question':'Who had compiled the album "Techno! The New Dance Sound Of Detroit"?','answer':'a','options':['a.Neil Rushton and Derrick May','b.Eddie Fowlkes and James Pennington','c.Keith Tucker and Carl Craig','d.Thomas Brinkmann and Frankie Bones']})
